<resources>
    <string name="app_name">tutorial_menu</string>
    <string name="openDrawerContentDesc">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawerContentDesc">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="guide_tab_introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="guide_tab_showcase">Showcase</string>
    <string name="guide_showcase_start_showcase">Show Me</string>
    <string name="guide_showcase_learn_more">Learn More</string>
    
    <string name="showcase_card1_title">Reminders</string>
    <string name="showcase_card1_subtitle">Sets reminders that alert you</string>
    <string name="showcase_card1_description">
        Customize your reminders with this versatile tool that lets you set personalized alerts for appointments, events, medication timings, and more. Tailor notifications to your schedule, ensuring you never miss an important moment.
    </string>

    <string name="showcase_card2_title">Contacts</string>
    <string name="showcase_card2_subtitle">Sets up contacts for easy access</string>
    <string name="showcase_card2_description">
        Add your contacts and assign photos to each one for easy access. Double-tap a contact\'s button to instantly place a call, making communication quick and personalized.
    </string>

    <string name="showcase_card3_title">Fences</string>
    <string name="showcase_card3_subtitle">Set up geo-fences and receive alerts</string>
    <string name="showcase_card3_description">
        Caregivers can set geo-fences to monitor patient movements, receiving alerts if fences are crossed.\n
        Patients can view the fences but not modify them, ensuring safety and peace of mind.
    </string>

    <string name="showcase_card4_title">Chat Buddy</string>
    <string name="showcase_card4_subtitle">Talk with a friendly AI</string>
    <string name="showcase_card4_description">Engage in daily banter or ask questions, making your interactions enjoyable and livening up the day.</string>

    <string name="docs_card1_title">Reminders</string>
    <string name="docs_card1_description">
        The reminders tool will help you create handy notes that alert you based on datetime set by you.\n\n

        On the reminders tool\'s home screen, you can select the group you want to view currently by selecting the appropriate icon with the group name underneath.\n
        Thereby, any reminders under the selected group will be displayed. Clicking on any of the reminders will allow you to edit them if necessary.\n
        If you wish to delete any reminders that you have already done, you can simply click the empty circle next to the reminder.\n\n

        When you start creating a new Reminder, you can choose to either select a pre-existing group or create a new one.\n
        This is to provide a way to categorize each Reminder to tailor to your needs, allowing you to sort them accordingly as needed.\n\n

        The Title of the Reminder will be what is displayed on notifications as well as on the Reminders.\n
        Subsequently, the Notes section allow you to input any additional information regarding the Reminder.\n\n

        The Schedule date indicates the deadline of the Reminder, which is the date that the Repeat interval will be based upon.\n
        An alert is triggered on the day of the Schedule date as well.\n\n

        The Reminders section allows you to add multiple date and time points, each of which will trigger an alert accordingly as well.\n
        These date/time points will be automatically re-calculated accordingly if the Reminder has a Repeat interval set.\n\n

        The Repeat section allows you to select the interval that the Reminder will repeat again based on the Schedule date.\n
        You can also create a customized repeat interval if necessary.\n\n

        The Ringtone section allows you to either turn on or off a ringtone that plays when the alert triggers.\n
        You can also set any .mp3 or .wav file from your system files as the ringtone.\n

    </string>

    <string name="docs_card2_title">Contacts</string>
    <string name="docs_card2_description">CONTACTS</string>

    <string name="docs_card3_title">Fences</string>
    <string name="docs_card3_description">FENCES</string>

    <string name="docs_card4_title">Chat Buddy</string>
    <string name="docs_card4_description">CHAT BUDDY</string>
</resources>